Archibald M. Crossley Papers 1999.0007
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series I: Consumer Studies, undated, 1927-1969
  - Subseries A: Radio, undated, 1927-1950
    - Station WOR
      - Greater NY Radio Listening Study Report (No. 27), 1943 August - September (Box 5:, Folder 198)
      - Greater NY Radio Listening Study Report (No. 28), 1943 September - October (Box 5:, Folder 199)
      - Greater NY Radio Listening Study Report (No. 29), 1943 October - November (Box 5:, Folder 200)
      - Greater NY Radio Listening Study Report (No. 30), 1943 November - December (Box 5:, Folder 201)
      - Greater NY Radio Listening Study Report (No. 31), 1943 December - 1944 January (Box 5:, Folder 202)
      - Greater NY Radio Listening Study Report (No. 32), 1944 January - February (Box 5:, Folder 203)
      - Station Indices, 1944 January - 1945 January (Box 5:, Folder 204)
      - Greater NY Radio Listening Study Report (No. 33), 1944 February - March (Box 5:, Folder 205)
      - Greater NY Radio Listening Study Report (No. 34), 1944 March - April (Box 5:, Folder 206)
      - Greater NY Radio Listening Study Report (No. 35), 1944 April - May (Box 5:, Folder 207)
      - Greater NY Radio Listening Study Report (No. 36), 1944 May - June (Box 5:, Folder 208)
      - Greater NY Radio Listening Study Report (No. 37), 1944 June - July (Box 5:, Folder 209)
      - Greater NY Radio Listening Study Report (No. 38), 1944 July - August (Box 5:, Folder 210)
      - Greater NY Radio Listening Study Report (No. 39), 1944 August - September (Box 5:, Folder 211)
      - Greater NY Radio Listening Study Report (No. 40), 1944 September - October (Box 5:, Folder 212)
      - Listening Families by Demographics Qualitative Report, 1944 September - December (Box 5:, Folder 213)
      - WOR/Cooperative Analysis of Broadcasting (C.A.B.) Comparative Share of Audience Study (analysis only), 1944 September - 1945 December (Box 5:, Folder 214)
      - Greater NY Radio Listening Study Report (World Series), 1944 October (Box 5:, Folder 215)
      - Greater NY Radio Listening Study Report (No. 41), 1944 October - November (Box 5:, Folder 216)
      - Greater NY Radio Listening Study Report (No. 42), 1944 November - December (Box 5:, Folder 217)
      - Greater NY Radio Listening Study Report (No. 43), 1944 December - 1945 January (Box 5:, Folder 218)
      - Greater NY Radio Listening Study Report (No. 44), 1945 January - February (Box 5:, Folder 219)
      - Listening Families by Demographics Qualitative Report, 1945 January - April (Box 5:, Folder 220)
      - Charted Time Invested in WOR Studies, 1945 January - December (Box 5:, Folder 221)
      - Station Indices, 1945 January - December (Box 5:, Folder 222)
      - Greater NY Radio Listening Study Report (No. 45), 1945 February - March (Box 5:, Folder 223)
      - Greater NY Radio Listening Study Report (No. 46), 1945 March - April (Box 5:, Folder 224)
      - Greater NY Radio Listening Study Report (No. 47), 1945 April - May (Box 5:, Folder 225)
      - Greater NY Radio Listening Study Report (No. 48), 1945 May - June (Box 5:, Folder 226)
      - Listening Families by Demographics Qualitative Report, 1945 May - August (Box 5:, Folder 227)
      - Greater NY Radio Listening Study Report (No. 49), 1945 June - July (Box 5:, Folder 228)
      - Greater NY Radio Listening Study Report (No. 50), 1945 July - August (Box 5:, Folder 229)
      - Greater NY Radio Listening Study Report (No. 51), 1945 August - September (Box 6:, Folder 230)
      - Greater NY Radio Listening Study Report (No. 52), 1945 September - October (Box 6:, Folder 231)
      - Small Station Report, 1945 September - October (Box 6:, Folder 232)
      - Listening Families by Demographics Qualitative Report, 1945 September - December (Box 6:, Folder 233)
      - Greater NY Radio Listening Study Report (No. 53), 1945 October - November (Box 6:, Folder 234)
      - Small Station Report, 1945 October - November (Box 6:, Folder 235)
      - Greater NY Radio Listening Study Report (No. 54), 1945 November - December (Box 6:, Folder 236)
      - Small Station Report, 1945 November - December (Box 6:, Folder 237)
      - Greater NY Radio Listening Study Report (No. 55), 1945 December - 1946 January (Box 6:, Folder 238)
      - Small Station Report, 1945 December - 1946 January (Box 6:, Folder 239)
      - Greater NY Radio Listening Study Report (No. 56), 1946 January - February (Box 6:, Folder 240)
      - Small Station Report, 1946 January - February (Box 6:, Folder 241)
      - Greater NY Radio Listening Study Report (No. 57), 1946 February - March (Box 6:, Folder 242)
      - Various Unidentified Studies' Surveys Materials, undated (Box 6:, Folder 243)
    - Unidentified Sponsors
      - Readership by Radio Executives Study, undated (Box 6:, Folder 244)
      - Coincidental Radio Studies (29 cities), 1938 November - 1939 March (Box 6:, Folder 245)
      - Coincidental Radio Studies (47 cities), 1939 March - June (Box 6:, Folder 246)
      - Coincidental Radio Studies (79 cities), 1939 July - November (Box 6:, Folder 247)
      - Coincidental Radio Studies (38 cities), 1939 November - 1940 March (Box 6:, Folder 248)
      - Coincidental Radio Studies (48 cities), 1940 November - 1941 May (Box 6:, Folder 249)
      - Coincidental Radio Studies (67 cities), 1941 June - 1942 January (Box 6:, Folder 250)
      - Coincidental Radio Studies (73 cities), 1942 February - October (Box 6:, Folder 251)
      - Radio Audience by Stations Study: Charleston, WV (analysis only), 1943 November - December (Box 6:, Folder 252)
      - Radio Listening in Metropolitan Syracuse, NY (analysis only), 1944 February - March (Box 6:, Folder 253)
      - Radio Listening in the 40-mile Market Area of Syracuse, NY (analysis only), 1944 February - March (Box 6:, Folder 254)
      - Station Indices in Major Markets of Syracuse, NY (analysis only), 1944 February - March (Box 6:, Folder 255)
      - Radio Listening Audience Size and Attitudes: New York, NY, Published Report, 1944 May (Box 6:, Folder 256)
      - Radio Audience by Stations Study: Ashland, KY (analysis only), 1944 September (Box 6:, Folder 257)
      - Radio Survey Test, 1946 December (Box 6:, Folder 258)
    - Western Gateway Broadcasting Corp.--Radio Audience to Baseball Study: Schenectady, NY, 1950 July (Box 6:, Folder 259)
  - Subseries B: Magazine/Newspaper, undated, 1935-1962
    - Architectural Forum--Post-War Housing Market Study, 1945 September (Box 7:, Folder 260)
    - Argosy Magazine--National Man Market Survey, 1948 October (Box 7:, Folder 261)
    - Argosy Magazine--Rate of Consumer Consumption Survey: Peoria, IL, 1949 November (Box 7:, Folder 262)
    - Association of National Advertisers--Farmer's Attitude Toward Business Survey, 1943 October (Box 7:, Folder 263)
    - Association of National Advertisers--Farmer's Attitude Toward Business Survey, 1944 October (Box 7:, Folder 264)
    - Association of National Advertisers--Farmer Attitude Study, 1950 September (Box 7:, Folder 265)
    - Automotive News--17-State Automotive News Reader Study, 1954 August (Box 7:, Folder 266)
    - Better Living Magazine--Shopping and Readership Among Women Study, 1951 August (Box 7:, Folder 267)
    - Coronet Magazine--Distribution and Sales Study: Rochester, NY, 1944 February (Box 7:, Folder 268)
    - Coronet Magazine--Editorial Study, 1944 June (Box 7:, Folder 269)
    - Coronet Magazine--Pilot Study: Omaha, NE, 1947 April (Box 7:, Folder 270)
    - Crowell Publishing Co.--Editorial Appeal of Three Women's Magazines Study, 1941 July - September (Box 7:, Folder 271)
    - Curtis Publishing Co.--Magazine Reading Habits Survey (incomplete tabulations only), 1935 February - March (Box 7:, Folder 272)
    - Curtis Publishing Co.--National Farm Media Survey, 1947 May (Box 7:, Folder 273)
    - Curtis Publishing Co.--Rural Counties Claimed Readership Study (tabulations only), 1947 June (Box 7:, Folder 274)
    - Esquire Magazine
      - Armed Forces Readership Study, Published Report, undated (Box 7:, Folder 275)
      - Urban Opinion of Calendar and Drawings Surveys, 1943 October (Box 7:, Folder 276)
      - Pilot Study, 1945 November - December (Box 7:, Folder 277)
      - Pilot Study: Indianapolis, IN, 1946 March (Box 7:, Folder 278)
      - Readership Study of Male College Students, 1949 March (Box 7:, Folder 279)
    - Fawcett Publications, Inc.--Continuing Study of Women, 1946 October (Box 7:, Folder 280)
    - Fawcett Publications, Inc.--Continuing Study of Women (supplemental tabulations), 1946 October (Box 7:, Folder 281)
    - Hearst Corp.
      - Product Endorsement Study No. 1, 1945 March (Box 7:, Folder 282)
      - Good Housekeeping Subscribers Survey, 1947 February (Box 7:, Folder 283)
      - Product Endorsement Study No. 2, 1953 October (Box 7:, Folder 284)
      - Product Endorsement Study No. 3, 1958 (Box 7:, Folder 285)
      - Product Endorsement Studies Reference Materials, undated (Box 7:, Folder 286)
    - Kaplan and Bruck--Newsstand Magazine Buyers Study, 1950 January (Box 7:, Folder 287)
    - Liberty Magazine, Inc.--Research Proposal Correspondence, 1948 March (Box 7:, Folder 288)
    - Life Magazine
      - Continuing Study of Magazine Audiences (CSMA)--Background and History, undated (Box 7:, Folder 289)
      - CSMA--Field Materials, undated (Box 7:, Folder 290)
      - CSMA--Methodology, undated (Box 7:, Folder 291)
      - CSMA--Published Report No. 1 (with supplemental pre-tests), 1938 December (Box 7:, Folder 292)
      - CSMA--Published Report No. 2 (with tabulation materials), 1939 May (Box 8:, Folder 293)
      - CSMA--Published Report No. 3, 1940 January (Box 8:, Folder 294)
      - CSMA--Published Report No. 3 Supplemental Data, undated (Box 8:, Folder 295)
      - CSMA--Published Report No. 4, 1940 September (Box 8:, Folder 296)
      - CSMA--Published Report No. 5, 1941 October (Box 8:, Folder 297)
      - CSMA--Published Report No. 5 Supplemental Data, undated (Box 8:, Folder 298)
      - Weekly Magazine Reading in the U.S. Armed Forces, 1942 [April - May] (Box 8:, Folder 299)
      - CSMA--Published Report No. 6, 1942 September (Box 8:, Folder 300)
      - The Magazine Ogre Report (analysis only), 1943 January (Box 8:, Folder 301)
      - The Impact of War on American Families Study, 1943 April (Box 8:, Folder 302)
      - CSMA--Published Report No. 7 (with supplemental data), 1943 November (Box 8:, Folder 303)
      - Men in the Armed Forces Survey (no tabulations), 1944 January (Box 8:, Folder 304)
      - War Brides and Young Mothers Study, [1944 February] (Box 8:, Folder 305)
      - CSMA--Published Report No. 8 (with supplemental data), 1946 August (Box 8:, Folder 306)
      - CSMA--A Matter of Consuming Interest Study, Published Report, [1947] (Box 8:, Folder 307)
      - CSMA--Analysis of the Continuing Study of Magazine Audiences, 1947 January (Box 8:, Folder 308)
      - CSMA--Published Report No. 9, 1947 November (Box 8:, Folder 309)
      - CSMA--Published Report No. 9 Supplemental Data, undated (Box 8:, Folder 310)
      - CSMA--Special Autos and Audiences Report (based on CSMA Published Report No. 9), 1947 November (Box 8:, Folder 311)
      - Subscriber Telephone Survey (tabulations only), 1948 March (Box 8:, Folder 312)
    - Look Magazine
      - Research and Development, undated (Box 8:, Folder 313)
      - Sales and Promotions, undated (Box 8:, Folder 314)
      - National Audience Study No. 1--Field Materials, 1946 September (Box 8:, Folder 315)
      - National Audience Study No. 1--Published Report (with supplemental data), 1946 September (Box 8:, Folder 316)
      - National Audience Study No. 1--Sampling, undated (Box 8:, Folder 317)
      - National Audience Study No. 2, 1947 (Box 8:, Folder 318)
      - National Audience Study No. 3, 1948 (Box 8:, Folder 319)
      - Relative Preferences For Collier's and Look Study (tabulations only), 1948 September (Box 8:, Folder 320)
      - Retail Executives and Sales Personnell Reading Habits Study: Lancaster, PA (tabulations only), 1948 December (Box 8:, Folder 321)
      - National Audience Study No. 4, 1949 (Box 8:, Folder 322)
      - Retail Executives and Sales Personnell Reading Habits Study: Riverside, CA (tabulations only), 1949 April (Box 8:, Folder 323)
      - Drug Store Outlets Reading Habits Study: Fort Wayne, IN (tabulations only), 1949 August (Box 8:, Folder 324)
      - Motor Vehicle Dealers Reading Habits Study: Detroit, MI (tabulations only), 1949 September (Box 8:, Folder 325)
      - The Cleveland Studies--Field Materials, undated (Box 9:, Folder 326)
      - The Cleveland Studies--Published Report (with supplemental data), 1950 (Box 9:, Folder 327)
      - Super-Markets Reading Habits Study: Cleveland, OH (tabulations only), 1950 April (Box 9:, Folder 328)
      - New Ford Car Buyers Reading Habits Study: Cleveland, OH (tabulations only), 1950 August (Box 9:, Folder 329)
      - Editorial Items Study, 1951 March (Box 9:, Folder 330)
      - Reading Habits Study: Racine, WI--Correspondence, 1950 May - 1951 May (Box 9:, Folder 331)
      - Reading Habits Study: Racine, WI--Field Materials, undated (Box 9:, Folder 332)
      - Reading Habits Study: Racine, WI, 1951 March - April (Box 9:, Folder 333)
      - Reading Habits Study: Racine, WI--Supplemental Materials, undated (Box 9:, Folder 334)
      - National Audience Study No. 5--Field Materials, undated (Box 9:, Folder 335)
      - National Audience Study No. 5--Methodology, undated (Box 9:, Folder 336)
      - National Audience Study No. 5--Published Report, 1952 (Box 9:, Folder 337)
      - National Audience Study No. 5--Sampling, undated (Box 9:, Folder 338)
      - National Audience Study No. 5--Supplemental Data, undated (Box 9:, Folder 339)
      - National Audience Study No. 5--Supplemental Data, undated (Box 9:, Folder 340)
      - National Audience Study No. 5--1952 Report Review, 1953 January (Box 9:, Folder 341)
      - National Audience Studies Appraisals--Comments and Notes, undated (Box 9:, Folder 342)
      - National Audience Studies Appraisals--Correspondences, 1952 June - 1953 December (Box 9:, Folder 343)
      - National Audience Studies Appraisal Reports, 1953 May, 1954 (Box 9:, Folder 344)
    - Magazine Audience Group (MAG)
      - Background and History, undated (Box 9:, Folder 345)
      - Finances, undated (Box 9:, Folder 346)
      - Methodology, undated (Box 9:, Folder 347)
      - Syracuse Magazine Study, 1944 July (Box 9:, Folder 348)
      - Analysis of Magazine Audiences, Published Report, 1948 (Box 9:, Folder 349)
      - True Story Women's Group Study, Published Report, 1949 (Box 9:, Folder 350)
      - Joint Multiple Magazine Study (Williamsport Pilot), 1953 October (Box 9:, Folder 351)
    - McCall Corp.--News Survey: Detroit, MI (tabulations only), undated (Box 9:, Folder 352)
    - McCall Corp.--Magazine Reading Study Proposal, 1943 September (Box 9:, Folder 353)
    - McFadden Publications, Inc.
      - Bathroom Shelf Inventory Study (tabulations only), undated (Box 10:, Folder 354)
      - Food Store Buying Study, Published Report, undated (Box 10:, Folder 355)
      - American Weekly and True Story Magazine Study, 1936 November (Box 10:, Folder 356)
      - Wage Earner Forum (tabulations only), 1944 (Box 10:, Folder 357)
      - Wage Earner Forum (further tabulations), undated (Box 10:, Folder 358)
      - Various Correspondences, 1944 February - 1945 February (Box 10:, Folder 359)
      - Supermarket Studies Background Information and Supplemental Tabulations, undated (Box 10:, Folder 360)
      - Supermarket Study, Published Report, 1948 (Box 10:, Folder 361)
      - Magazine Audiences Study: Cincinnati, OH, 1951 February - March (Box 10:, Folder 362)
      - Magazine Audiences Study: Cincinnati, OH, Published Report, 1951 (Box 10:, Folder 363)
      - Grocery Outlet Expenditure Study: Cincinnati, OH, 1951 July (Box 10:, Folder 364)
      - Food Store Buying Study, 1952 October (Box 10:, Folder 365)
      - Supermarket Study: Indianapolis, IN (tabulations only), 1952 October (Box 10:, Folder 366)
      - Audit Study (tabulations only), 1954 April (Box 10:, Folder 367)
      - Supermarket Basket Check Study, 1954 July (Box 10:, Folder 368)
      - Wage Earner Forum Publication, 1962 May (Box 10:, Folder 369)
    - McGraw Hill Publishing Co., Inc.
      - American Machinist Study, undated (Box 10:, Folder 370)
      - Unidentified Business Weekly Survey, undated (Box 10:, Folder 371)
      - American Industry Study Proposal, 1937 April (Box 10:, Folder 372)
      - Business Week Subscriber Study, 1937 October - November (Box 10:, Folder 373)
      - Industrial Reading Habits Study, 1943 March (Box 10:, Folder 374)
      - Industrial Reading Habits Study Supplemental Tabulations, 1943 March (Box 10:, Folder 375)
      - Business Week Subscriber Pilot Study: Cleveland, OH, 1948 October (Box 10:, Folder 376)
      - Business Week Subscriber Pilot Study: St. Louis, MO, 1948 October (Box 10:, Folder 377)
      - Unidentified Mailing Study Tabulations, 1950 (Box 10:, Folder 378)
      - Electrical Contractor Readership Study, 1950 April (Box 10:, Folder 379)
      - Electrical Contractor Readership Study: Hartford, CT, 1950 April (Box 10:, Folder 380)
      - Electrical Contractor Readership Study: Indianapolis, IN, [1950 April] (Box 10:, Folder 381)
      - Electrical Contractor Readership Study: Minneapolis, MN, [1950 April] (Box 10:, Folder 382)
      - Most Useful Magazine Mail Study (tabulations only), 1950 May (Box 10:, Folder 383)
      - Useful Publications Serving the Coal Mining Industry (tabulations only), 1950 August (Box 10:, Folder 384)
      - Industry-Wide Magazine Preference Study, 1951 (Box 10:, Folder 385)
      - Food Field Magazine Readership Study, 1951 August (Box 10:, Folder 386)
      - Magazine Readership Study (tabulations only), 1951 August (Box 10:, Folder 387)
      - Retail Outlets Trade Publication Reading Study, 1952 March (Box 10:, Folder 388)
      - Textile Mill Magazine Preferences Study (tabulations only), 1952 July (Box 10:, Folder 389)
      - Baking Industry Study, Published Report, [1954] (Box 10:, Folder 390)
      - Electric Utilities Industry Readership Study, Published Report, [1954] (Box 10:, Folder 391)
      - Materials Handling Equipment Study, Published Report, [1954] (Box 10:, Folder 392)
      - Textile Industry Study, Published Report, [1954] (Box 10:, Folder 393)
      - Magazine Reading Mail Report, 1954 April (Box 10:, Folder 394)
      - Railroad Executives Magazine Readership Study, Published Report, [1954 August] (Box 10:, Folder 395)
      - Federal Trade Commission Hearing, 1960 February (Box 10:, Folder 396)
    - Meredith Publishing Co.--National Better Homes and Gardens Reader Study, 1947 February (Box 11:, Folder 397)
    - Miscellaneous Reference Materials, undated (Box 11:, Folder 398)
    - New York Herald-Tribune--Former Subscriber Readership Study (tabulations only), 1945 October (Box 11:, Folder 399)
    - New York Times-- New York Newspapers Readership Study, 1948 March (Box 11:, Folder 400)
    - New York Times--Sunday Times Survey Proposal, 1948 November (Box 11:, Folder 401)
    - New York Times--Reading Traffic of the New York Times Study (tabulations only), 1949 January (Box 11:, Folder 402)
    - Our World Publishing Co.--Magazine Article Preferences (working questionnaire), 1952 August (Box 11:, Folder 403)
    - Pageant Magazine--Editorial Study, 1946 June (Box 11:, Folder 404)
    - Pageant Magazine--Editorial Study Field Materials, 1946 June (Box 11:, Folder 405)
    - Parents' Institute, Inc.--Baby Care Manual Readership Study (with published report), 1952 August (Box 11:, Folder 406)
    - Parents' Magazine--Readership Study, 1953 August (Box 11:, Folder 407)
    - Parents' Magazine--Readership Study, 1953 October (Box 11:, Folder 408)
    - Parents' Magazine--Readership Study, 1953 November (Box 11:, Folder 409)
    - Progressive Farmer Magazine
      - Southern State Farm and Home Equipment Study (with published report), 1945 November (Box 11:, Folder 410)
      - Southern Farm Study, 1946 February (Box 11:, Folder 411)
      - National Farm Market Coverage Study, Published Report, 1949 (Box 11:, Folder 412)
      - Southern Farm Study (with published report), 1949 April - May (Box 11:, Folder 413)
      - Southern Farms Study (with published report), 1952 May - June (Box 11:, Folder 414)
      - Study Proposal, 1954 March (Box 11:, Folder 415)
    - Reader's Digest Association, Inc.--Study Proposal, 1958 May (Box 11:, Folder 416)
    - Street and Smith Publications, Inc.--Shelter Magazine Audience Study, 1954 September (Box 11:, Folder 417)
    - Time, Inc.
      - Time Magazine Newsstand Buyers Study, 1946 January (Box 11:, Folder 418)
      - Time Subscribers Home Ownership Survey, 1946 January (Box 11:, Folder 419)
      - Reading and Noting Study (tabulations only), 1947 April (Box 11:, Folder 420)
      - Reading and Noting Study, 1947 May (Box 11:, Folder 421)
      - Reading and Noting Study (tabulations only), 1947 May (Box 11:, Folder 422)
      - Continuing Reading and Noting Study (tabulations only), 1947 July (Box 11:, Folder 423)
      - Current Affairs Survey: Dayton, OH, 1947 July (Box 11:, Folder 424)
      - Continuing Reading and Noting Study (tabulations only), 1947 August (Box 11:, Folder 425)
      - Continuing Reading and Noting Study (tabulations only), 1947 September (Box 11:, Folder 426)
      - Time Subscriber Telephone Survey, 1948 March (Box 11:, Folder 427)
      - Federal Government Executives Magazine Readership Survey, 1949 February (Box 11:, Folder 428)
      - Leisure Time Study Proposal, 1949 November (Box 11:, Folder 429)
      - Magazine Reading Survey, 1950 April (Box 11:, Folder 430)
      - Recent Time Subscription Expiration Survey, 1950 May (Box 11:, Folder 431)
      - Continuing Reading and Noting Study, 1950 September (Box 11:, Folder 432)
      - Continuing Reading and Noting Study, 1950 October (Box 11:, Folder 433)
      - Continuing Reading and Noting Study, 1950 December (Box 11:, Folder 434)
      - Continuing Reading and Noting Study (with supplemental tabulations), 1951 January (Box 11:, Folder 435)
      - Continuing Reading and Noting Study, 1951 May (Box 11:, Folder 436)
      - Continuing Reading and Noting Study, 1951 June (Box 11:, Folder 437)
      - Continuing Reading and Noting Study, 1951 July (Box 11:, Folder 438)
      - Continuing Reading and Noting Study, 1951 October (Box 11:, Folder 439)
      - Continuing Reading and Noting Study, 1951 December (Box 11:, Folder 440)
    - Unidentified Sponsor--Comic Section Preferences Study: Richmond, VA, 1936 November (Box 11:, Folder 441)
    - Unidentified Sponsor--Comic Strip Reading Study: Cleveland, OH (tabulations only), 1942 July (Box 11:, Folder 442)
    - Unidentified Sponsor--Comic Strip Reading Study (tabulations only), 1942 December (Box 11:, Folder 443)
    - Unidentified Sponsor--Reading Intensity Study, 1952 July - August (Box 11:, Folder 444)
    - W.D. Hoard and Sons Co. Publishers--Hoard's Dairyman Subscribers' Home and Farm Study, 1953 August (Box 11:, Folder 445)
    - Weekly Newspaper Bureau--Weekly Newspaper Circulation Analysis (including sampling), 1947 May (Box 11:, Folder 446)
    - Weekly Newspaper Bureau--Weekly Newspaper Circulation Study, Correspondences, 1946 March - 1947 October (Box 11:, Folder 447)
    - Weekly Newspaper Bureau--Typical Market Areas Study: Wisconsin Areas, 1948 May (Box 11:, Folder 448)
  - Subseries C: Various, undated, 1928-1969
    - Abbott Kimball Co., Inc.
      - Silk Consumer Study ( Rochester, NY, Daily Report No. 1), 1947 November (Box 12:, Folder 449)
      - Silk Consumer Study, [1947 December] (Box 12:, Folder 450)